Let's freeze it and then make its tail
I just said that its width is 8 mm
I made it 8 mm high
The width is 200 mm
You can adjust it later
It seems not long enough
Make it longer
Almost like this
Then make it the internal line
Make it two internal lines
What to do
I'll know in a moment
Make it two
Two internal lines
Then use this quick arrangement
Arrange it
Change it
Use this
Turn it over
Turn it back
Why do this
To make an ear and a tail
Add a fixing pin
I'll simulate it later
See this
In order to stabilize
Because this plate is too small
Add two fixing pins
Then sew it
When sewing
Take off the end of the ruler
From the second and third internal lines
Just these two
Then I will
And this one
Why do you add fixing pins
You'll know later
You can directly match
I don't match
Why
I want to make two different tails
Don't make a symmetry for it
So
And then we put this one and this one inside this short one to separate
You can pull it out a little bit to check if your sewing line is reversed
There is no reverse here
And then I want to make it more realistic here
Make a knot because we have a knot when we tie
I can activate this here
Make the overlap and contrast of these two panels lower to 1
Make it flat a little bit
But their thickness has to come out to 1
Modify
Now this place is too small
It's not convenient for me to make a knot later
Because I want to put a knot in
So here you can consider
Use your hand to open the simulation and pull it down
Pause the simulation
In this way
It's like pulling out a hole
Freeze it
Next, let's make its knot
Make this knot width
Suppose for example 8mm
I'll draw one at random
Because this can be adjusted later
So it doesn't matter
Then make two internal lines for it
What for
For the next one
We need to be able to make a knot
To make another knot
Take the whole with the knot
For example, make a knot
You can also use this
Then we will twist it
I'll make a knot
We need to do it
Then we can fold it
If you want to do this
Then you can use the folding tool
To do it
This small plate of particles is lowered to it
Because it is very small
Then it is very dangerous in this position
So directly lowered to 1
Then, the above and below simulation
That's a good simulation
You can just cover it up
Then these two internal lines can be deleted
Then this plate
You can slowly tighten it by adjusting its length
Then I used a function here
Maybe too fast
Choose two sides
There is a line section in the right key here
And the built-in internal line
The default is directly a center line
Then cut it off
What to do with the cut off
You can do one
For example, the above and below
The above and below
Combine it up and down
Because this knot is a bit too hard
Just a knot like this
It's probably a bit too hard on it
So you can just go up and down
So that he has a mistake in this knot
Then tighten it up a little bit
Conflict thickness
You can consider lowering it a little bit
Increase the thickness of the membrane
This knot will do
Wait for it to be frozen
Two bags are activated
Take the fixed needle
I pressed control w
Delete the fixed needle for him
Put it down
Let me help you
Then on these two bags
This zero-degree fold line is deleted
Take it down
Pull it a little bit
Prevent it from being too big
it is good
This bag is finished
well
This is the end of the video
Thank you for watching
See you in the next video
Bye